Mannes - Damrosch Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, 1911-61 and undated (Box 7, Box 35)
  Subject files consist of letters, printed clippings from magazines and newspapers, printed and typescript brochures and programs, photographs, burial documents.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject, then chronologically
  - Damrosch Memorial, Woodlawn Cemetery, 1948, n.d.
    - Correspondence, Photographs, Miscellaneous (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Marker impression (Box-folder 35/12)
  - Music School Settlement for Colored People, 1911-61, n.d. (Box-folder 7/2)
- Miscellaneous (Box 7, Box 33)
  Miscellaneous consists of locks of hair, contents of wallet, and lists.
  Arranged alphabetically by person
  - Blow, David
    - Locks of hair, age of 3 weeks and 3 years (in sealed envelopes) (Box-folder 7/3)
  - [Damrosch, Leopold]
    - Wallet (Box-folder 33/3)
    - Wallet Contents, Contents: Ich singe dir mit Herz und Mund..., music sketch in ink, n.d.; photograph of Helene Von Heimburg Damrosch; lock of hair; and decorative printed card, n.d. (Box-folder 7/4)
  - Mannes, David
    - List of donors to the town hall chair in honor of David Mannes, n.d. (Box-folder 7/5)
  - Mannes, Marya
    - List of Reporter staff, 1963 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - Unidentified person, lock of hair, n.d. (Box-folder 7/7)